{"id": "job_00000", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "is", "hiring", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "SQL", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00001", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "position", ",", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00002", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Seattle.", "Skills", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00003", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Austin", "needs", "Product", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "Agile."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00004", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "with", "project", "management", "to", "join", "Digital", "Ventures", "in", "Chicago."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00005", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "in", "Boston", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00006", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "position", ",", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00007", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "project", "management", "to", "join", "NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00008", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", "located", "in", "Chicago.", "Must", "have", "data", "analysis", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00009", "tokens": ["Seeking", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", "located", "in", "Los", "Angeles.", "Must", "have", "JavaScript", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00010", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "communication", "to", "join", "InnovateLabs", "in", "Austin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00011", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "in", "Austin", "with", "JavaScript", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00012", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", "located", "in", "Atlanta.", "Must", "have", "communication", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00013", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "in", "Atlanta", "needs", "Software", "Engineer", "proficient", "in", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00014", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Seattle.", "Skills", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00015", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "in", "Chicago", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00016", "tokens": ["Join", "CloudServices", "as", "a", "UX", "Designer", "!", "Location", ":", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00017", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00018", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Sales", "Representative", "position", ",", "CloudServices", ",", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00019", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Sales", "Representative", "position", ",", "CloudServices", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00020", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "Marketing", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00021", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Product", "Manager", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Skills", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00022", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "SmartTech.", "Requirements", ":", "machine", "learning.", "Location", ":", "Seattle."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00023", "tokens": ["Join", "FutureSoft", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00024", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Product", "Manager", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "InnovateLabs", "in", "Chicago."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00025", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "New", "York.", "Skills", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00026", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Product", "Manager", "position", ",", "SmartTech", ",", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00027", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Product", "Manager", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "Digital", "Ventures", "in", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00028", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "(", "San", "Francisco", ")", "seeks", "UX", "Designer.", "Must", "know", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00029", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "is", "hiring", "a", "Product", "Manager", "in", "Boston", "with", "communication", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00030", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "project", "management", "to", "join", "PrimeTech", "in", "Denver."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00031", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "in", "Chicago", "needs", "Data", "Scientist", "proficient", "in", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00032", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Marketing", "Manager", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", "located", "in", "Los", "Angeles.", "Must", "have", "SQL", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00033", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Product", "Manager", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "New", "York.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00034", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "cloud", "computing", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00035", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "in", "San", "Francisco", "needs", "Marketing", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "Agile."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00036", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "at", "FutureSoft", ",", "San", "Francisco.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00037", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "NextGen", "Industries.", "Requirements", ":", "cloud", "computing.", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00038", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Product", "Manager", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Portland.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00039", "tokens": ["Product", "Manager", "role", "at", "TechCorp", ",", "Chicago.", "Key", "skill", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00040", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00041", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Austin", "needs", "Data", "Scientist", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00042", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00043", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "UX", "Designer", "position", ",", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00044", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00045", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Product", "Manager", "at", "CloudServices", ",", "Seattle.", "Skills", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00046", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "Digital", "Ventures.", "Requirements", ":", "communication.", "Location", ":", "New", "York."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00047", "tokens": ["Join", "TechCorp", "as", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00048", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "position", ",", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00049", "tokens": ["Join", "PrimeTech", "as", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00050", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "in", "San", "Francisco", "needs", "Financial", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "Agile."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00051", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Product", "Manager", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Austin.", "Must", "have", "project", "management", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00052", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00053", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "leadership", "to", "join", "CloudServices", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00054", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "is", "hiring", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "project", "management", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00055", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00056", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Financial", "Analyst", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00057", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "in", "Denver", "with", "cloud", "computing", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00058", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Denver."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00059", "tokens": ["Join", "NextGen", "Industries", "as", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00060", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Product", "Manager", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00061", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "in", "Atlanta", "needs", "Data", "Scientist", "proficient", "in", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00062", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "role", "at", "FutureSoft", ",", "Denver.", "Key", "skill", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00063", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "with", "communication", "to", "join", "NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Chicago."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00064", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "is", "hiring", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "in", "Boston", "with", "Python", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00065", "tokens": ["Financial", "Analyst", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "project", "management.", "Location", ":", "New", "York."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00066", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Product", "Manager", "position", ",", "TechCorp", ",", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00067", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "cloud", "computing", "to", "join", "InnovateLabs", "in", "Seattle."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00068", "tokens": ["Seeking", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Atlanta.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00069", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "in", "Boston", "with", "JavaScript", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00070", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00071", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "is", "hiring", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "data", "analysis", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00072", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00073", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "Agile", "to", "join", "NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Denver."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00074", "tokens": ["Join", "NextGen", "Industries", "as", "a", "UX", "Designer", "!", "Location", ":", "New", "York.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00075", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "TechCorp", ",", "Austin.", "Skills", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00076", "tokens": ["Join", "SmartTech", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00077", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "role", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Chicago.", "Key", "skill", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00078", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "(", "New", "York", ")", "seeks", "Software", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00079", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "position", ",", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00080", "tokens": ["Digital", "Ventures", "in", "Chicago", "needs", "Financial", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00081", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "needs", "DevOps", "Engineer", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00082", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "UX", "Designer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "San", "Francisco.", "Skills", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00083", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "Agile.", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00084", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "PrimeTech", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00085", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Product", "Manager", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00086", "tokens": ["Seeking", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "TechCorp", "located", "in", "Chicago.", "Must", "have", "SQL", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00087", "tokens": ["Join", "Global", "Solutions", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco.", "Required", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00088", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "role", "at", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Denver.", "Key", "skill", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00089", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "(", "Los", "Angeles", ")", "seeks", "UX", "Designer.", "Must", "know", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00090", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Product", "Manager", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Los", "Angeles.", "Must", "have", "data", "analysis", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00091", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "in", "Boston", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00092", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "position", ",", "PrimeTech", ",", "New", "York.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00093", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "position", ",", "InnovateLabs", ",", "New", "York.", "Required", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00094", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "with", "Python", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Chicago."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00095", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "role", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Seattle.", "Key", "skill", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00096", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", "located", "in", "Portland.", "Must", "have", "cloud", "computing", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00097", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "Business", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00098", "tokens": ["Business", "Analyst", "position", "available", "at", "SmartTech.", "Requirements", ":", "cloud", "computing.", "Location", ":", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00099", "tokens": ["Product", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc.", "Requirements", ":", "Agile.", "Location", ":", "Seattle."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00100", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "needs", "Business", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00101", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "Digital", "Ventures.", "Requirements", ":", "communication.", "Location", ":", "Boston."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00102", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "UX", "Designer", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00103", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Financial", "Analyst", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Austin.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00104", "tokens": ["Join", "CloudServices", "as", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00105", "tokens": ["Data", "Scientist", "role", "at", "InnovateLabs", ",", "New", "York.", "Key", "skill", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00106", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00107", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "role", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Denver.", "Key", "skill", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00108", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "(", "San", "Francisco", ")", "seeks", "UX", "Designer.", "Must", "know", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00109", "tokens": ["Product", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "NextGen", "Industries.", "Requirements", ":", "Python.", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00110", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "with", "Python", "to", "join", "Digital", "Ventures", "in", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00111", "tokens": ["Join", "PrimeTech", "as", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "!", "Location", ":", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00112", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "FutureSoft.", "Requirements", ":", "Agile.", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00113", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Portland.", "Skills", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00114", "tokens": ["Financial", "Analyst", "role", "at", "CloudServices", ",", "Atlanta.", "Key", "skill", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00115", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "UX", "Designer", "with", "data", "analysis", "to", "join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00116", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "role", "at", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Key", "skill", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00117", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "role", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Austin.", "Key", "skill", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00118", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "(", "Seattle", ")", "seeks", "Financial", "Analyst.", "Must", "know", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00119", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "Digital", "Ventures.", "Requirements", ":", "data", "analysis.", "Location", ":", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00120", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "UX", "Designer", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00121", "tokens": ["UX", "Designer", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "cloud", "computing.", "Location", ":", "Austin."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00122", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "New", "York.", "Skills", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00123", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "FutureSoft.", "Requirements", ":", "project", "management.", "Location", ":", "Chicago."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00124", "tokens": ["Join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "as", "a", "UX", "Designer", "!", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00125", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "SmartTech", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00126", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "data", "analysis.", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00127", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "position", ",", "SmartTech", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Required", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00128", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "Python", "to", "join", "FutureSoft", "in", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00129", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Austin", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "Agile."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00130", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "(", "New", "York", ")", "seeks", "DevOps", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00131", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "in", "Denver", "needs", "Data", "Scientist", "proficient", "in", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00132", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Marketing", "Manager", "at", "InnovateLabs", "located", "in", "San", "Francisco.", "Must", "have", "communication", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00133", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Product", "Manager", "with", "data", "analysis", "to", "join", "PrimeTech", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00134", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Atlanta", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00135", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "with", "communication", "to", "join", "SmartTech", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00136", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "is", "hiring", "a", "Product", "Manager", "in", "Boston", "with", "SQL", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00137", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "FutureSoft", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00138", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "data", "analysis", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00139", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "with", "cloud", "computing", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00140", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "role", "at", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "New", "York.", "Key", "skill", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00141", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc.", "Requirements", ":", "JavaScript.", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00142", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "CloudServices", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00143", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "Agile.", "Location", ":", "Boston."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00144", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "is", "hiring", "a", "Product", "Manager", "in", "Chicago", "with", "machine", "learning", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00145", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "UX", "Designer", "position", ",", "FutureSoft", ",", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00146", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "UX", "Designer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Seattle.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00147", "tokens": ["Digital", "Ventures", "is", "hiring", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "in", "Atlanta", "with", "cloud", "computing", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00148", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "role", "at", "FutureSoft", ",", "Denver.", "Key", "skill", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00149", "tokens": ["Join", "CloudServices", "as", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00150", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "FutureSoft.", "Requirements", ":", "cloud", "computing.", "Location", ":", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00151", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "is", "hiring", "a", "UX", "Designer", "in", "New", "York", "with", "Agile", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00152", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Chicago", "needs", "Financial", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00153", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Product", "Manager", "with", "Agile", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00154", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "Data", "Scientist", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00155", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00156", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "(", "Boston", ")", "seeks", "Sales", "Representative.", "Must", "know", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00157", "tokens": ["Financial", "Analyst", "role", "at", "PrimeTech", ",", "Austin.", "Key", "skill", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00158", "tokens": ["Seeking", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", "located", "in", "Portland.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00159", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Product", "Manager", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", "located", "in", "Austin.", "Must", "have", "Agile", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00160", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "Global", "Solutions.", "Requirements", ":", "JavaScript.", "Location", ":", "New", "York."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00161", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "project", "management", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00162", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "position", ",", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "San", "Francisco.", "Required", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00163", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "UX", "Designer", "at", "CloudServices", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Skills", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00164", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "in", "New", "York", "needs", "Marketing", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00165", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00166", "tokens": ["Join", "CloudServices", "as", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00167", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Sales", "Representative", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "New", "York.", "Must", "have", "communication", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00168", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Denver.", "Skills", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00169", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "position", "available", "at", "Digital", "Ventures.", "Requirements", ":", "data", "analysis.", "Location", ":", "Austin."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00170", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "machine", "learning", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00171", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Portland", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00172", "tokens": ["Join", "Global", "Solutions", "as", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00173", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "Software", "Engineer", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00174", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Chicago."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00175", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Austin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00176", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "data", "analysis.", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00177", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", "located", "in", "Boston.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00178", "tokens": ["Join", "Digital", "Ventures", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00179", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "FutureSoft", ",", "Boston.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00180", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "PrimeTech", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00181", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "Global", "Solutions.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "Austin."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00182", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "New", "York.", "Skills", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00183", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "is", "hiring", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "in", "New", "York", "with", "data", "analysis", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00184", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "leadership", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00185", "tokens": ["Join", "TechCorp", "as", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles.", "Required", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00186", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Financial", "Analyst", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Atlanta.", "Must", "have", "SQL", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00187", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Denver", "needs", "Product", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00188", "tokens": ["UX", "Designer", "role", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "Boston.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00189", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "is", "hiring", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "in", "Austin", "with", "Agile", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00190", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "Boston."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00191", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "with", "cloud", "computing", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00192", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "(", "San", "Francisco", ")", "seeks", "Software", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00193", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "(", "Portland", ")", "seeks", "Sales", "Representative.", "Must", "know", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00194", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00195", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "role", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Denver.", "Key", "skill", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00196", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "is", "hiring", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "in", "New", "York", "with", "machine", "learning", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00197", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "UX", "Designer", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00198", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Product", "Manager", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", "located", "in", "New", "York.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00199", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Atlanta.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00200", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "is", "hiring", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "in", "Portland", "with", "machine", "learning", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00201", "tokens": ["Join", "NextGen", "Industries", "as", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Denver.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00202", "tokens": ["Join", "Global", "Solutions", "as", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles.", "Required", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00203", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "SmartTech", "located", "in", "Boston.", "Must", "have", "machine", "learning", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00204", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "(", "Portland", ")", "seeks", "Data", "Scientist.", "Must", "know", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00205", "tokens": ["Business", "Analyst", "role", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Portland.", "Key", "skill", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00206", "tokens": ["Join", "SmartTech", "as", "a", "UX", "Designer", "!", "Location", ":", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00207", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "in", "Chicago", "needs", "Product", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00208", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "CloudServices", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00209", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "position", ",", "PrimeTech", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00210", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", "located", "in", "New", "York.", "Must", "have", "communication", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00211", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Financial", "Analyst", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00212", "tokens": ["Join", "Global", "Solutions", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00213", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Marketing", "Manager", "at", "InnovateLabs", "located", "in", "Atlanta.", "Must", "have", "project", "management", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00214", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "(", "San", "Francisco", ")", "seeks", "Software", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00215", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "(", "San", "Francisco", ")", "seeks", "Financial", "Analyst.", "Must", "know", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00216", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "machine", "learning", "to", "join", "SmartTech", "in", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00217", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "is", "hiring", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "in", "Chicago", "with", "Agile", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00218", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "is", "hiring", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "in", "Denver", "with", "cloud", "computing", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00219", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Sales", "Representative", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", "located", "in", "Chicago.", "Must", "have", "data", "analysis", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00220", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Financial", "Analyst", "at", "Global", "Solutions", "located", "in", "San", "Francisco.", "Must", "have", "SQL", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00221", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "(", "Portland", ")", "seeks", "DevOps", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00222", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "(", "San", "Francisco", ")", "seeks", "Financial", "Analyst.", "Must", "know", "Python."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00223", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Chicago.", "Must", "have", "Agile", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00224", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "PrimeTech", "in", "Atlanta."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00225", "tokens": ["Product", "Manager", "role", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00226", "tokens": ["Business", "Analyst", "role", "at", "PrimeTech", ",", "Atlanta.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00227", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Seattle."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00228", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "position", ",", "PrimeTech", ",", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00229", "tokens": ["Data", "Scientist", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "Chicago."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00230", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "Marketing", "Manager", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00231", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Portland.", "Skills", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00232", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Austin.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00233", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "SmartTech.", "Requirements", ":", "Agile.", "Location", ":", "New", "York."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00234", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "in", "Portland", "needs", "Sales", "Representative", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00235", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "in", "San", "Francisco", "needs", "Business", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00236", "tokens": ["Financial", "Analyst", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "Python.", "Location", ":", "Portland."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00237", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "with", "machine", "learning", "to", "join", "FutureSoft", "in", "Seattle."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00238", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "with", "Python", "to", "join", "FutureSoft", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00239", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Financial", "Analyst", "at", "PrimeTech", ",", "Boston.", "Skills", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00240", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00241", "tokens": ["Seeking", "UX", "Designer", "at", "InnovateLabs", "located", "in", "Austin.", "Must", "have", "Agile", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00242", "tokens": ["InnovateLabs", "is", "hiring", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "in", "Austin", "with", "SQL", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00243", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "in", "Seattle", "needs", "Software", "Engineer", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00244", "tokens": ["Join", "Digital", "Ventures", "as", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00245", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "position", ",", "TechCorp", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00246", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "position", ",", "TechCorp", ",", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00247", "tokens": ["Seeking", "UX", "Designer", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", "located", "in", "Denver.", "Must", "have", "cloud", "computing", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00248", "tokens": ["Data", "Scientist", "position", "available", "at", "Digital", "Ventures.", "Requirements", ":", "Agile.", "Location", ":", "Austin."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00249", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "(", "Portland", ")", "seeks", "Product", "Manager.", "Must", "know", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00250", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "Digital", "Ventures.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "Boston."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00251", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "UX", "Designer", "at", "CloudServices", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Skills", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00252", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "in", "Boston", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00253", "tokens": ["Data", "Scientist", "role", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "Seattle.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00254", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Sales", "Representative", "at", "PrimeTech", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Skills", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00255", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "(", "Denver", ")", "seeks", "HR", "Specialist.", "Must", "know", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00256", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "position", ",", "SmartTech", ",", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00257", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "(", "Seattle", ")", "seeks", "Business", "Analyst.", "Must", "know", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00258", "tokens": ["UX", "Designer", "role", "at", "FutureSoft", ",", "Denver.", "Key", "skill", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00259", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "New", "York", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00260", "tokens": ["Seeking", "UX", "Designer", "at", "InnovateLabs", "located", "in", "Austin.", "Must", "have", "machine", "learning", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00261", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "position", ",", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00262", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "UX", "Designer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Denver.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00263", "tokens": ["Seeking", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "TechCorp", "located", "in", "Seattle.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00264", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "TechCorp", ",", "Boston.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00265", "tokens": ["Financial", "Analyst", "role", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "San", "Francisco.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00266", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00267", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "(", "Seattle", ")", "seeks", "Data", "Scientist.", "Must", "know", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00268", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "role", "at", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Key", "skill", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00269", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Product", "Manager", "at", "DataSystems", "Inc", "located", "in", "Chicago.", "Must", "have", "communication", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00270", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00271", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "in", "Atlanta", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00272", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "is", "hiring", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "in", "New", "York", "with", "leadership", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00273", "tokens": ["Digital", "Ventures", "in", "Portland", "needs", "Business", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00274", "tokens": ["CloudServices", "is", "hiring", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "JavaScript", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00275", "tokens": ["Join", "CloudServices", "as", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00276", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "needs", "Business", "Analyst", "proficient", "in", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00277", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "TechCorp", "located", "in", "Boston.", "Must", "have", "data", "analysis", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00278", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "(", "Chicago", ")", "seeks", "UX", "Designer.", "Must", "know", "communication."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00279", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "TechCorp", ",", "Boston.", "Skills", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00280", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "in", "New", "York", "needs", "Data", "Scientist", "proficient", "in", "project", "management."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00281", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "SmartTech", "located", "in", "Seattle.", "Must", "have", "Agile", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00282", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "UX", "Designer", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Austin.", "Skills", ":", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00283", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "UX", "Designer", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "Agile", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00284", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "role", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Chicago.", "Key", "skill", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00285", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00286", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Financial", "Analyst", "position", ",", "CloudServices", ",", "Portland.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00287", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "in", "San", "Francisco", "needs", "Sales", "Representative", "proficient", "in", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00288", "tokens": ["Join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00289", "tokens": ["Join", "NextGen", "Industries", "as", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "!", "Location", ":", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00290", "tokens": ["Data", "Scientist", "position", "available", "at", "TechCorp.", "Requirements", ":", "cloud", "computing.", "Location", ":", "Portland."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00291", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Sales", "Representative", "at", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "Atlanta.", "Skills", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00292", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "(", "Atlanta", ")", "seeks", "DevOps", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00293", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00294", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Austin.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00295", "tokens": ["Seeking", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "InnovateLabs", "located", "in", "Atlanta.", "Must", "have", "communication", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00296", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00297", "tokens": ["Data", "Scientist", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "JavaScript.", "Location", ":", "Boston."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00298", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "project", "management", "to", "join", "PrimeTech", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00299", "tokens": ["Join", "SmartTech", "as", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "!", "Location", ":", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00300", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "Boston."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00301", "tokens": ["SmartTech", "(", "Los", "Angeles", ")", "seeks", "Sales", "Representative.", "Must", "know", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00302", "tokens": ["Join", "SmartTech", "as", "a", "Product", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "New", "York.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00303", "tokens": ["Join", "SmartTech", "as", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00304", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Product", "Manager", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "DataSystems", "Inc", "in", "Austin."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00305", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "role", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "Austin.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00306", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "Global", "Solutions.", "Requirements", ":", "JavaScript.", "Location", ":", "Chicago."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00307", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Product", "Manager", "with", "Agile", "to", "join", "Digital", "Ventures", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00308", "tokens": ["Business", "Analyst", "role", "at", "PrimeTech", ",", "New", "York.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00309", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "role", "at", "Global", "Solutions", ",", "Portland.", "Key", "skill", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00310", "tokens": ["UX", "Designer", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "cloud", "computing.", "Location", ":", "Chicago."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00311", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "!", "Location", ":", "Boston.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00312", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "with", "JavaScript", "to", "join", "CloudServices", "in", "Seattle."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00313", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Financial", "Analyst", "position", ",", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "Agile."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00314", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Product", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00315", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "role", "at", "FutureSoft", ",", "Seattle.", "Key", "skill", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00316", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "CloudServices", "located", "in", "Seattle.", "Must", "have", "Python", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00317", "tokens": ["Join", "TechCorp", "as", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00318", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "communication", "to", "join", "InnovateLabs", "in", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00319", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "SmartTech.", "Requirements", ":", "JavaScript.", "Location", ":", "Denver."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00320", "tokens": ["Join", "PrimeTech", "as", "a", "Product", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00321", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "Seattle.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00322", "tokens": ["UX", "Designer", "position", "available", "at", "CloudServices.", "Requirements", ":", "machine", "learning.", "Location", ":", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00323", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Product", "Manager", "position", ",", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Austin.", "Required", ":", "communication."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00324", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "role", "at", "TechCorp", ",", "Boston.", "Key", "skill", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00325", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "CloudServices", "located", "in", "Portland.", "Must", "have", "leadership", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00326", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "New", "York.", "Skills", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00327", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "UX", "Designer", "with", "project", "management", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Portland."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00328", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "position", ",", "PrimeTech", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00329", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "needs", "Sales", "Representative", "proficient", "in", "SQL."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00330", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "in", "Portland", "needs", "DevOps", "Engineer", "proficient", "in", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00331", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "with", "leadership", "to", "join", "Digital", "Ventures", "in", "New", "York."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00332", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "Chicago.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00333", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "role", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "Austin.", "Key", "skill", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00334", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "Global", "Solutions.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00335", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Business", "Analyst", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Portland.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00336", "tokens": ["Join", "InnovateLabs", "as", "a", "Marketing", "Manager", "!", "Location", ":", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "Python."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00337", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "with", "cloud", "computing", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00338", "tokens": ["Marketing", "Manager", "position", "available", "at", "InnovateLabs.", "Requirements", ":", "leadership.", "Location", ":", "New", "York."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00339", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "leadership", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Denver."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00340", "tokens": ["HR", "Specialist", "position", "available", "at", "NextGen", "Industries.", "Requirements", ":", "project", "management.", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00341", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "SmartTech", ",", "New", "York.", "Skills", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00342", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "is", "hiring", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "in", "Austin", "with", "data", "analysis", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00343", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "TechCorp", ",", "Boston.", "Skills", ":", "SQL."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00344", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Sales", "Representative", "with", "SQL", "to", "join", "Global", "Solutions", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00345", "tokens": ["UX", "Designer", "role", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Boston.", "Key", "skill", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00346", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "in", "Denver", "needs", "UX", "Designer", "proficient", "in", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00347", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "Marketing", "Manager", "position", ",", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "Los", "Angeles.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00348", "tokens": ["TechCorp", "is", "hiring", "a", "Product", "Manager", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "with", "communication", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00349", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Product", "Manager", "at", "InnovateLabs", ",", "Boston.", "Skills", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00350", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "in", "Portland", "needs", "HR", "Specialist", "proficient", "in", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00351", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "Software", "Engineer", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Seattle.", "Skills", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00352", "tokens": ["Join", "NextGen", "Industries", "as", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "leadership."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00353", "tokens": ["Software", "Engineer", "position", "available", "at", "PrimeTech.", "Requirements", ":", "Python.", "Location", ":", "San", "Francisco."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00354", "tokens": ["DevOps", "Engineer", "role", "at", "NextGen", "Industries", ",", "Seattle.", "Key", "skill", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00355", "tokens": ["NextGen", "Industries", "is", "hiring", "a", "Financial", "Analyst", "in", "Chicago", "with", "leadership", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00356", "tokens": ["Digital", "Ventures", "(", "Portland", ")", "seeks", "DevOps", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "leadership."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00357", "tokens": ["FutureSoft", "is", "hiring", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "in", "San", "Francisco", "with", "JavaScript", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00358", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "with", "Agile", "to", "join", "FutureSoft", "in", "Boston."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00359", "tokens": ["Excellent", "opportunity", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "at", "PrimeTech", ",", "Chicago.", "Skills", ":", "cloud", "computing."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00360", "tokens": ["Financial", "Analyst", "role", "at", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "San", "Francisco.", "Key", "skill", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00361", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "is", "hiring", "a", "HR", "Specialist", "in", "Portland", "with", "JavaScript", "experience."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00362", "tokens": ["DataSystems", "Inc", "(", "Seattle", ")", "seeks", "Product", "Manager.", "Must", "know", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00363", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Data", "Scientist", "at", "PrimeTech", "located", "in", "Portland.", "Must", "have", "Python", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00364", "tokens": ["Sales", "Representative", "position", "available", "at", "FutureSoft.", "Requirements", ":", "Python.", "Location", ":", "New", "York."], "labels": ["B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00365", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "UX", "Designer", "position", ",", "Digital", "Ventures", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00366", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "DevOps", "Engineer", "with", "Agile", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Chicago."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00367", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "HR", "Specialist", "position", ",", "TechCorp", ",", "Seattle.", "Required", ":", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00368", "tokens": ["We're", "looking", "for", "a", "Data", "Scientist", "with", "cloud", "computing", "to", "join", "TechCorp", "in", "Los", "Angeles."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-SKILL", "I-SKILL", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00369", "tokens": ["Join", "TechCorp", "as", "a", "Business", "Analyst", "!", "Location", ":", "Atlanta.", "Required", ":", "data", "analysis."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00370", "tokens": ["Global", "Solutions", "(", "Austin", ")", "seeks", "DevOps", "Engineer.", "Must", "know", "Agile."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00371", "tokens": ["Seeking", "Sales", "Representative", "at", "CloudServices", "located", "in", "Portland.", "Must", "have", "Python", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00372", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "(", "Denver", ")", "seeks", "Business", "Analyst.", "Must", "know", "JavaScript."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00373", "tokens": ["Apply", "now", ":", "DevOps", "Engineer", "position", ",", "DataSystems", "Inc", ",", "New", "York.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00374", "tokens": ["Seeking", "HR", "Specialist", "at", "Global", "Solutions", "located", "in", "Atlanta.", "Must", "have", "SQL", "skills."], "labels": ["O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SKILL", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00375", "tokens": ["Join", "Digital", "Ventures", "as", "a", "Software", "Engineer", "!", "Location", ":", "Chicago.", "Required", ":", "project", "management."], "labels": ["O", "B-COMPANY", "I-COMPANY", "O", "O", "B-JOBTITLE", "I-JOBTITLE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "job_00376", "tokens": ["PrimeTech", "(", "Los", "Angeles", ")", "seeks", "UX", "Designer.", "Must", "know", "machine", "learning."], "labels": ["B-COMPANY", "O", "B-LOCATION", "I-LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
